[Music]
Hi everyone, welcome back to the channel. So let's
start today's video. If we
talk about yesterday's market art,
after the Asian market closed with a sell-off, we
saw profit booking again in the US market. The
Dow Jones Industrial Average (API) 500 is seen at 0.59 and 1.1
for Monday. So, you may
see the market opening gap down on Monday, after which we can expect
a further downside due to profit booking.
You can also confirm this by going to the median level here.
So let's look at our stock
list further. The
first stock in the list has
seen a significant decline in the last few trading hours.
Due to profit booking, the stock is
continuously trading downwards here.
If we talk about yesterday's trading hours,
we saw a significant sell-off here yesterday as well,
and the stock is quite close to its previous support.  It is
closing close to closing.
This makes one thing clear: if you
see the market opening on Monday,
you may see a strong selling stock in it, and you can plan to short it here. So, let's
talk about Bharti.
We saw a fall of around 4 in Friday's trading session. Even
on its futures side, you will see a strong
downside going forward because
we can see a lot of open interest build-up in its option contract on the selling
side. So, if you
see it opening below 435 on Monday,
you can plan to sell the stock with targets of 430 and 428.
After this, in the next stock, a
significant downside can be seen here for the last few weeks.
After a significant rally, we can see profit booking
extending here,
which can be
clearly seen from its 15-minute candle.
Even in daily candles, you'll
see profit booking here
because it's very close to support. If
this support breaks, you might see a further selling opportunity
in the stock during trading hours on Monday.
So, we're talking about a pharma
stock, Lupin Limited. On
Friday, a fall of around 1.8% can be
seen here.
Even on its future side, we can
plan for a selling stock on Monday. So,
if you see it opening below 900,
you
can plan for two stocks between 900 and 895. So, if you want to connect with us in real time,
join the Tegra channel below, the link to which you'll
find in the description and pinned comment.
If you like this video,
you
can see your feedback in the form of a like.
You can also share the video with others
to increase our reach and we  We will continue to bring you
such information in the future.
So let's look at our third
stock. The third stock in the list shows
profit booking after a significant rally,
which is clearly visible on its 15-
minute candle.
Because its Q2 results were
slightly negative,
you may see marginal selling pressure here for the next two to three days.
If the stock opens gap down,
you need to immediately
plan your sell trade.
We are talking about Just Dial, which
closed on Friday with a fall of around 4.45. For
now, if you see this stock
opening below 650 on Monday,
you may see a selling opportunity in it for the future.
In that scenario, you can plan two target stocks of 645 and 640.
Finally,
if we talk about the fourth stock,
So, the stock has been
highly volatile and consolidating for some time now.
In the last trading session,
we witnessed selling with high volume. So,
if
you see this stock opening this week,
you may see its previous support being
reached, and
in that scenario, you
can book a good profit here. So, we are
again talking about a pharma stock
which was forming its highs in the last six months
with a rally around 500. For
now,
you see it falling slightly due to profit booking.
So, for now,
you may see a selling opportunity from its order book.
In this scenario, you
can place your sell order in the stock below 30020.
In that scenario, you may see
two targets here at 315 and 30014.
If you
see it opening gap down, you can invest in it.  You
can extend your sell trade to 312 as a target. If you have
any issues placing your target and stop-loss,
we've uploaded a video related to this.
You'll find a link
in the description section.
You can also check out intraday and mutual fund-related
playlists there.
Finally, we'll talk about Nifty and Bank
Nifty.
After opening at 11,675 on Friday, it
reached a high near 11,750.
Due to some selling,
it finally
closed at 1164. For
now, you
can see a consolidation here on the daily candles.
If you see a gap-down opening here on Monday,
we could see some selling pressure.
If we were to
understand this from the weekly options data,
we could see
an immediate support forming near 11,600 on the put side.  In
this case,
if you see this support breaking, then the
next support can be
seen at 11500 because
currently
a build-up of around 1.5 million open interest contracts can be
seen here at these two levels. On the call side,
11600 appears to be a challenge for us
because at this level, we see
700,000 calls being added in the in-the-money call contracts,
and at this
level, we can see a build-up of a total of 1191,000 open interest
contracts. In
this case, if Nifty is
successful in sustaining this level, then the
next resistance can be
seen at 11700
because at this level we can see
a build-up of around 1678 open interest contracts.
Next,
if we check Bank Nifty,
despite opening flat like Nifty,
it reached its
high at 24000 (273) and
later saw a sell-off.  Due to this, it has
closed at 23900,
so we still see selling in it
because we are seeing profit booking at such a
high level for now. With the
US
elections coming up, the market may remain volatile,
so you should consider this before taking any fresh entry in Bank Nifty on the
buy side.
If we
check out its weekly option chain, for
now you will see
marginal put writing in the in-the-money put contracts above 24000,
but
due to profit booking, we can
see immediate support near 23000/500
because around 3.45
lakh open interest contracts can be
seen here at this level. Even if this sell-off continues further,
we can see strong
support here at the 23000 level
because of around
52000 open interest contracts.
We can see a build-up here. The
first resistance for us on the call side will be the
24,000 level
because currently 3,79,000
open interest contracts can be seen building up at this level.
If
Bank Nifty opens below this level and tries to
return and reclaim it, then
you may
see the market consolidating here.
Otherwise, due to profit booking,
you may see a trading range
between 23,500 and 24,000
in Bank Nifty on Monday. So,
with this, let's start with this video. If you like the video,
like it. And if
you haven't subscribed to our channel yet,
you can subscribe to it to get daily
stock market and personal finance related
updates.
[Music]